Hit me baby, one more time.
Hitman's Wife's Bodyguard is a action, comedy,
crime film directed by Patrick Hughes.
The world’s most lethal odd couple – bodyguard Michael Bryce and hitman
Darius Kincaid – are back on another life-threatening mission.
Still unlicensed and under scrutiny, Bryce is forced into action by Darius's even more
volatile wife, the infamous international con artist Sonia Kincaid.
As Bryce is driven over the edge by his two most dangerous protectees, the trio get in over their heads in a global
plot and soon find that they are all that stand between Europe and a vengeful and powerful madman.
Michael Bryce, played by Ryan Reynolds.
Darius Kincaid, played by Samuel L. Jackson.
Sonia Kincaid, played by Salma Hayek Pinault.
Aristotle Papdopolous, played by Antonio Banderas.
Senior, played by Morgan Freeman.
Bobby O'Neill, played by Frank Grillo.
Hitman's Wife's Bodyguard is a 2021 American action comedy film directed by Patrick
Hughes and written by Tom O'Connor and Brandon and Phillip Murphy.
The film is a sequel to the 2017 film The Hitman's
Bodyguard and features Ryan Reynolds, Samuel L.
Jackson, Salma Hayek, and Richard E.
Grant reprising their roles, with Frank Grillo, Antonio
Banderas, and Morgan Freeman joining the cast.
In the film, suspended bodyguard Michael Bryce (Reynolds) must once again team up with hitman Darius Kincaid
(Jackson) and his wife, Sonia (Hayek), to stop a madman (Banderas) from launching a terror attack on Europe.
Hitman's Wife's Bodyguard was theatrically released in the
United States on June 16, 2021, by Lionsgate.
The film received negative reviews from critics and flopped at the box office, grossing
$70.1 million on a $70 million budget, less than half its predecessor.
The film explores themes of hitman, bodyguard, sequel,
aftercreditsstinger, duringcreditsstinger.
The tone is lighthearted and intense.